techvibes.com 2017-06-25

# Techvibes: Privacy Policy – Techvibes

**Overview**

Techvibes collects e-mail addresses of people who send us e-mail and information they may provide to us. We also collect information about what pages visitors to our web site access and information provided to us by site visitors, prospective clients who contact or engage with us regarding our services. This information may contain personal data about our prospective and active customers such address, phone numbers and demographic or other personal information that they provide to us. We also host and process from time to time user data that clients or others submit to us under the services or deliverables produced by us and used by clients and others.     In sum we collect two types of data: (1) client or prospective client   data used to set up and manage your account and our relationship with you    (2) End user data that we may possess, host, or process that is submitted by end users of our services and deliverables.

We will not disclose personal information without your written permission. Some information collected we obtain about you is in the context of us providing our services to you. We do not share, sell, or rent the information we receive with others except in limited circumstances where your use of Techvibes indicates a valid consent to disclose. For example:

  1. Techvibes may disclose personal information to investigate, prevent, or take action about actual or suspected illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations that may involve potential threats to the physical safety someone, violations of Techvibes’s terms and conditions, or as otherwise required by law.

  2. Techvibes employs other companies and suppliers  to perform tasks on our behalf and we may need to share your information with them to provide products and services to you, in which case we do so under conditions of confidentiality and only to the extent necessary for the purpose at hand.

  3. Techvibes may also share your information to provide products or services you or end users requested or when we have your permission, such as when you use a Techvibes service or deliverable to log in to a third-party web site.

  4. We will transfer information about you if Techvibes is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Techvibes will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Techvibes web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

  5. We will also disclose information if we are required to under a law enforcement investigation or in response to a subpoena, in which case we will try and limit disclosure while complying with our legal obligations. ** **

**What we do with your information, Consent to Electronic Messages**

The term “Personal Information” as used here is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person who such information relates to. Personal Information that we collect will be subject to this Privacy Policy, which may be amended from time to time.

When you register with Techvibes or engage with us as an actual or prospective Client we ask for information that may include your name, company name, email address, billing address, credit card or payment information and perhaps some demographic information. Techvibes uses the information we collect for these general purposes: to offer,  provide and support Techvibes or its affiliate or partner companies products and services including consulting, events, learning and training opportunities, technology and industry developments, course instruction, billing, identification and authentication and security purposes, product and service improvement, support and maintenance, research, and follow up sales and marketing.  By registering or maintaining an account with us, you consent to receiving electronic messages and other communications in order to maintain that account, to provide services to you, and to promote existing or new services or offerings to you from time to time.

**Security**

The security of your personal information and data that you store on our service is important to us. We encrypt the transmission of personal information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and AES-256 encryption. We follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage method is completely secure. While we endeavor to use commercially acceptable methods and standards to protect your personal information, we are unable guarantee absolute security. Where applicable, Techvibes protects credit card information using industry-standard Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS).

**Disclosure**

Techvibes may from time to time use third party service providers to provide certain services to you directly or under sub-contract to Techvibes and we may share personal information with such service providers under confidentiality and in a manner that corresponds to our obligations under this Privacy Policy and standard industry practices.

Techvibes may disclose Personal Information under special circumstances, such as to comply with court orders requiring us to do so or to others when your actions violate the Terms of Use applicable to Techvibes and we need to take steps to enforce our Terms of Use. We do not sell, rent, loan or otherwise transfer Personal Information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services unless you provide your consent to that.

**Client Data Storage and Hosting**

Techvibes uses third party data storage and hosting services that use industry-standard security to store personal information including User Data that you submit to our service. Techvibes does not claim any ownership or right to use your Personal Information or user data and the respective end user and you retain all rights to such data except as provided in any applicable terms and conditions, end user agreements, services agreements, or statement of work.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small portion of data that may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Computers that access our website is assigned a different cookie by us which we use to track visitors to our web site. You are able in the privacy settings on your computer or browser to prohibit cookies.

**Google Analytics and Remarketing, Web Site Metrics and Analytics**

We may use a service from Google called Google Analytics (GA) or similar services from other service providers, which permit us to reach people who have visited our site previously, and display to them relevant advertisements when they visit other sites across the Internet that belong to the Google Display Network. This is called ‘remarketing’.

Cookies can be used to track your session on our or another website and serve customized advertising from Google and different third party vendors. When you visit a website you may look at advertisements posted on that site by Google or other third parties. Through first-party and third-party cookies, the third parties may collect information about you while you are visiting the website and other websites and use this data to show you advertisements on this website and across the Internet based on your sites visited on the Internet. For this activity, we do not collect this information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see; it is controlled by third parties such as Google.

**Opting Out, Managing Your Personal Information**

You can access and control your customer registration and encrypted personal data directly in your Techvibes account. You may be able to opt out of personalized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager (http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) and/or the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on (http://www.google.ca/ads/preferences/plugin/).

If you use of our website without opting out then we understand that you agree to data collection to provide you with remarketing ads using GA or cookies from other third party vendors based on your prior visits to our website and other sites on the Internet.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Techvibes reserves the right to modify our privacy statement at any time, so please review it from time to time. If we make significant changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by a notice on our homepage so you continue to be aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

For more information please contact contact@techvibes.com.
